[{"question": " are you kidding me?! joey. joey! joey! joey! joey! joey! joey! joey! joey! joey!!", "answer": "  joey. joey. joey. joey! joey!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " gunther, can i get another cup of coffee, please?  so uh, what do you do when you\u0092re not working here?", "answer": " you don\u0092t need to fill these silences.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " chandler, that\u0092s like your fourth cup of coffee!", "answer": " well, i am drinking lots of cups of coffee because i\u0092m exhausted! because joey started snoring!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " he\u0092s in a different room! he\u0092s really that loud?", "answer": "  oh, you should here me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " it\u0092s not something to be proud of, okay? you have to go to a sleep clinic!", "answer": " look, i told ya, i\u0092m not going to any clinic! i don\u0092t have a problem, you\u0092re the one with the problem! you should go to a \"quit being a baby and leave me alone\" clinic!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " they don\u0092t have those.", "answer": " yeah, they do! quit being a baby and leave me alone! there, you\u0092ve just had your first class!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " y\u0092know i used to go out with this guy that was a really light sleeper, and whenever i started to snore, he would just roll me over\u009a", "answer": " ohhh, yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " he would just roll me over and i would stop snoring.", "answer": " next time you snore, i\u0092m rolling ya over!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " i gotta do what i gotta do, you gotta do what you gotta do, you just do", "answer": "  hey guys!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " hey, all right!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh, the olympics.", "answer": " have you guys picked a date yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh no, not yet.", "answer": " i still cannot believe you\u0092re engaged!  just \u0091cause its happening so fast; not \u0091cause you\u0092re such a loser.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " oh. thanks. uh, has anyone seen rach?", "answer": " ugh, she\u0092s upstairs not doing the dishes! and i tell ya something! i\u0092m not doing them this time! i don\u0092t care if those dishes sit in the sink until they\u0092re all covered with\u0097i\u0092ll do them when i get home!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " yeah\u0097oh! hey listen umm, emily found this wedding dress in london\u009a", "answer": " already?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " yeah, but it didn\u0092t fit. well, luckily there\u0092s a store here that has one left in her size, but i\u0092m the groom, i\u0092m not supposed to see the dress\u009a", "answer": " i\u0092ll pick it up for you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh, she\u0092s got you running errands, y\u0092know, picking up wedding dresses\u009a  wah-pah!", "answer": " what\u0092s wah-pah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " y\u0092know, whipped! wah-pah!", "answer": " that\u0092s not whipped! whipped is wh-tcssh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " that\u0092s what i did. wah-pah!", "answer": " you can\u0092t do anything!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " hey, mon, i was just doing the dishes!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " oh! it\u0092s you.  hi.", "answer": " hey, do uh, do you have a minute?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " yeah, yeah, i was just about to take a break anyways, so\u009a", "answer": " so listen uh, i know you and i haven\u0092t really had a chance to talk since uh, emily and i decided to get married, and uh, i was just wondering how you were.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " oh.", "answer": " i know if you were getting married i\u0092d feel, kinda\u009a.. y\u0092know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " yeah. yeah. definitely, well it definitely took me by surprise, but i\u0092m okay.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " all right, i just wanted to check.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " you\u0092re great. and i-i know someday this will happen for you too. you just hang in there.", "answer": "  uhh, hang in there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh, no, i didn\u0092t mean, uh\u009a", "answer": " i mean maybe you didn\u0092t hear about a serious relationship called me and joshua?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh, i thought you guys had just been on like four dates, i didn\u0092t realise that had become anything, yet.", "answer": " oh, no-no-no, no-no-no, it has become, it has\u0097yeah. oh no, those were four great dates.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " oh. yeah?", "answer": " yeah. oh, yeah. and i mean, the connection, i mean y\u0092know, emotionally, mentally, physically\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " wow, that\u0092s-that\u0092s-that\u0092s incredible.", "answer": " i know isn\u0092t it? it\u0092s like i\u0092m right there with joshua.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " you are right there with emily. and it\u0092s y\u0092know, it\u0092s kinda like\u009a. it\u0092s a tie! well, i gotta get, i gotta get back to the dishes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " i gotta get to work.", "answer": " oh yeah? fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " hey, y\u0092know, y\u0092know what would make me really happy?", "answer": " oh yeah, no, what\u0092s that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " if like the four of us could all y\u0092know, hang out together. uh, in fact emily\u0092s coming into town this weekend, why don\u0092t you say we all have dinner? say, sunday night?", "answer": " that would be great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  did you say something?", "answer": " no, just singing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh my god! ohh! look at this one! it\u0092s so beautiful!", "answer": " yeah, but y\u0092know, about have of these are gonna end up getting divorced.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " may i help you ladies?", "answer": " oh, yes, umm, i\u0092m here to pick up a dress that you have on hold.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " yes, what\u0092s the name, please?", "answer": " emily waltham.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yes! i have it right here.  would you like to try it on ms. waltham?", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " you\u0092re the most beautiful bride i\u0092ve ever seen.", "answer": " i am, aren\u0092t i?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " ms. waltham?", "answer": " yes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " we\u0092re closing.", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " oh. thank you. ohhh, thank you very much. oh, thank you for coming.  uh, just a second!", "answer": " no-no, let me in!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " phoebe?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " can you just hold on for one minute?", "answer": " no, you have to let me in right now!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " are you alone?", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " this sucks! i didn\u0092t know i had to stay up all night before i went to this stupid sleep clinic! i\u0092m so tired!", "answer": " it\u0092s 6:00.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " yeah, well\u009a", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " hey, i hear that you and joshua are going out to dinner with ross and emily, and i think that\u0092s, i think that\u0092s really cool.", "answer": " yeah, rach, i think you\u0092re handling that really well.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " handling it? what do you mean, handling it? there\u0092s nothing to handle. now, maybe i would have a problem with this if it wasn\u0092t for me and joshua. y\u0092know, they\u0092re not gonna get married anyway!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " come on! they rushed into this thing so fast it\u0092s ridiculous! i mean, they\u0092re gonna be engaged for like what? a year? and somewhere along the way, one of them is gonna realise what they\u0092ve done and they\u0092re call the whole thing off. i\u0092m telling ya, you\u0092re gonna be dancing at my wedding before you\u0092re dancing at there\u0092s.", "answer": " yeah, well, i don\u0092t dance at weddings.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " because weddings are a great place to meet women, and when i dance, i look like this\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " hey man.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " so, what are you guys doing four weeks from today?", "answer": " nothing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " nothing.", "answer": " i am\u009a  free!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " great! because emily and i are getting married in a month! joey and chandler: what?!", "answer": " yep!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " in a month?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " you mean, you mean 30 days?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " from now?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " well, that\u0092s great.", "answer": " yeah! yeah, emily always wanted to get married in this beautiful place that her parents got married, but it\u0092s going to be torn down, so\u009a i mean, i-i know it\u0092s crazy, but everything up \u0091til now has been so crazy, and i don\u0092t know, this just feels right. y\u0092know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": "  hey, rachel.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " what\u0092s up? you\u0092re voice sounded all squeaky on the phone.", "answer": " ohh, nothing, i just wanted to see you. see you and hug you.  see you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " great!", "answer": " yeah!  sit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  you okay?", "answer": " i\u0092m more than okay, i am really, really happy! wanna know why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " do i?", "answer": " \u0091cause i am really happy about us. i think we are, i think we are so on the right track! y\u0092know? i mean, i think we are working, i think we are clicking. y\u0092know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yeah, sure-sure, yeah, we\u0092re-we\u0092re-we\u0092re-we\u0092re-we\u0092re clicking.", "answer": " yeah-yeah, y\u0092know if-if there was just like one little area where i\u0097that i think we need\u0097we would need to work on; i-i would think it was we\u0092re just not crazy enough!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i-i gotta say, i-i-i-i\u0092m not too sure i agree with that.", "answer": " well, yeah, right, y\u0092know what? yeah, you\u0092re right, i mean, we no, we have our fun. yeah! but if \u009a\u009ai mean, i mean like craaaazy! y\u0092know? okay, all right. this is gonna, this is gonna sound y\u0092know, a little umm, hasty, but uh, just go with it. umm. ugh. what if we got married?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " oh, i know, i know, it\u0092s-it\u0092s so, it\u0092s so totally like, \"whoa! can we do this?\" y\u0092know, i mean, but i mean it just feels right! don\u0092t you think? it does! i mean, it just feels right, don\u0092t you think?", "answer": " wow! uhh, rachel uhh, you\u0092re a real special lady, but my divorce isn\u0092t final yet and, and, and we\u0092ve been on four days, so i\u0092m thinking \"no, but thanks.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " you idiot!!!!!", "answer": " your name, please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": "  hey, check out that girl! she is really hot!", "answer": "  yeah, she is. wow!  how you doin\u0092?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " you\u0092re coming on to the entire room!  i\u0092m chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " i\u0092m marjorie.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " hi.", "answer": " you mind if i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " so uh, what are you in for?", "answer": " i talk in my sleep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " what a coincidence, i listen in my sleep.", "answer": "  so why don\u0092t you give me your number?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " okay, ready?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " congratulations!", "answer": " thank you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " okay! my turn! my turn!", "answer": " okay!  okay, ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  yeah.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": "  that was a terrible throw!!", "answer": " i\u0092m not gonna right to you! that\u0092s not real!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " look at me! my big concern is what\u0092s real?!  oh my god. we\u0092re really sad, aren\u0092t we?", "answer": " yeah, i think we are.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " this isn\u0092t even my dress.", "answer": " well, at least you didn\u0092t rent yours from a store called, \"it\u0092s not too late.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " i\u0092m changing out of this.", "answer": " me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " in like a half-hour?", "answer": " me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " okay, throw it straight this time.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i\u0092m getting married next!!", "answer": " yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " i hate my regular clothes now! y\u0092know? i look down and-and i know that this isn\u0092t gonna be the most special day of my life.", "answer": " yeah. i mean it was kinda fun for a while, but didn\u0092t you start feeling silly?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " oh god.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh, you\u0092re such a cheater!", "answer": "  hello! little ones.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " so, is joey gonna stop snoring?", "answer": " yep! and! a beautiful woman agreed to go out with me.  joey wanted to ask her out, but uh, she picked me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh, how\u0092d that happen?", "answer": " because i\u0092m cooler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " no, seriously.", "answer": " well she\u0092s, she\u0092s the kinda girl\u0097joey was unconscious.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  hey you guys! what\u0092s happening?", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " what is that?", "answer": "  oh, they gave it to me at the sleep clinic, and it\u0092s gonna help me not to snore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " well, are you asleep right now, joe? \u0091cause i don\u0092t think you have to wear it unless you are!", "answer": "  i know i don\u0092t have too! it tastes good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": "  well, i just called joshua\u009a", "answer": " oh, how did it go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " well, i did my best to convince him that i\u0092m not some crazy girl who is dying to get married\u0097i\u0092m just going through a hard time.", "answer": " what did he say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " well uh, his answering machine was very understanding. ugh. i feel blue.", "answer": " ohh, sweetie!  hey, i bet you anything that he\u0092s gonna call you again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yeah, maybe, but i don\u0092t think i even care. i don\u0092t think he\u0092s the one i\u0092m sad about. y\u0092know, i know that i said that i am totally okay with ross getting married, but as it turns out, i don\u0092t think i\u0092m handling it all that well.", "answer": " yeah, maybe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " and i-i am just trying to figure out why.", "answer": " any luck?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " well, yeah, y\u0092know how ross and i were on again, off again, on again, off again? i guess i just figured that somewhere down the road, we would be on again.", "answer": " again. y\u0092know what? i think we all did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " so, i got us some reservations for sunday night, okay? how about, ernie\u0092s at 9 o\u0092clock?", "answer": " yeah, well, you uh, better make it for three.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh, see i-i don\u0092t know if we\u0092re gonna be hungry at three.", "answer": " three people. joshua\u0092s not gonna be there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " what happened?", "answer": " uh, well, i think, i think he broke up with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " noo. why?", "answer": " well, apparently he scares easy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " oh, rachel, i\u0092m-i\u0092m sorry.", "answer": " it\u0092s okay. sometimes, things don\u0092t work out the way you\u0092d thought they would.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": "  oh, hey, don\u0092t you have to go pick up emily?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " you okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": "  hey, y\u0092know what might cheer you up?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " y\u0092know, i gotta tell ya, this really does put in a better mood.", "answer": " oh, i wish there was a job where i could wear this all the time.  maybe someday, there will be.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " oh god! he\u0092s gonna come by and borrow some candles for his big date!", "answer": " oh, okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " no-no, rachel, don\u0092t get it! he can\u0092t see us!", "answer": " no, yeah! the groom cannot see the bride!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " i\u0092m not gonna marry chandler!", "answer": " not after this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " i gotta go.", "answer": " oh, wait, joshua! joshua!   yeah, well, that oughta do it. closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep20.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}]